PURITAT CHAMART

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



INTERESTING

- Clean Code
- Blockchain Technology
- Value Investing
- Nature
- Classical Music & Coffee

ABOUT ME

I am a qualified system engineer with six years of experience in system integration & factory automation. Fast learning, strong problem-solving skills. Happy to focus on designing the good software architectures, coding on both client & server side for the growth of the organization, as well as sharpen my professional skills in the best possible way in the IT sector as " junior software developer".

SKILLS

Programming Languages

- Low-level language: Ladder diagram, Function-block diagram, State diagram
- High-level language: HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6

Databases

• SQL: MySQL, MSSQL

• NoSQL: MongoDB, Firebase

Project Management Tools

Virtual Environment : VMware, Docker

Version Control : Git. GitHub

Network & Communication Protocols

• Industrial: ModBus, ProfiBus

Non-Industrial: EtherNetIP

Other Programming skills

Google Apps Script, Google Apps Sheet

EXPERIENCE

CONTROL SYSTEM ENGINEER

Synergetech Co., Ltd., Nonthaburi, Thailand Jul 2016 - Jan 2022 (5 years 7 months)

- Automation system designing both of hardware & software.
- PLC programming (Low level language for field-devices controller.)
- SCADA programming (User interface for factory operation.)
- Database programming for passing data from field automation system to ERP system.
- · Project startup & commissioning
- Third party device communication testing.

INTERN

Inspiretech Co., Ltd., Nonthaburi, Thailand Jun 2015 - Jul 2015 (2 months)

• Built the logic for the MRT ventilation system under mention of leader.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF AUTOMATION ENGINEERING

King Mongkut's Insitute of Technology Ladkrabang 2012 - 2016

- Built the solar cell monitoring system using Raspberry Pi & Arduino.
- Water quality monitoring node..

KNOW MF MORF

February 03 1994 was born in Ubon Ratchatani, Thailand. (28 years old)



0933957611



introbond.dev@gmail.com



Github profile

• A rookie in Github but loving it



Awards & cirtifications

- Personal website built with free Bootstrap (HTML + CSS) template under authorize license
- · Google Firebase for hosting the site